export const data = [
  {
    question: "Hallelujah is a song written by which Canadian recording artist?",
    option1: "Leonard Cohen",
    option2: "Kory Lefkowits",
    option3: "Ryan Letourneau ",
    option4: "Justin Bieber ",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which famous rapper is featured in Jack 2015 single called?",
    option1: "Kendrick Lamar",
    option2: "2 Chainz",
    option3: "Future",
    option4: "Fatman Scoop",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "The Singing Cowboy Gene Autry is credited with the first recording for all but which classic Christmas jingle?",
    option1: "White Christmas",
    option2: "Frosty the Snowman",
    option3: "Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer",
    option4: "Here Comes Santa Claus",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What Led Zeppelin album contains Stairway to Heaven?",
    option1: "Houses of the Holy",
    option2: "Physical Graffiti",
    option3: "Led Zeppelin III",
    option4: "Led Zeppelin IV",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "From which country did the song Gangnam Style originate from?",
    option1: "Japan",
    option2: "North Korea",
    option3: "South Korea",
    option4: "China",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Grande is a phrase from the song Gran Vals What is that song segment known as?",
    option1: "Nokia Tune",
    option2: "Hello Moto [Motorola Ringtone]",
    option3: "Droid Ringtone",
    option4: "Microsoft Ringtone",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the best selling album of 2015?",
    option1: "Adele, 25",
    option2: "Fetty Wap, Fetty Wap",
    option3: "Taylor Swift, 1989",
    option4: "Justin Bieber, Purpose",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Some people call me the space cowboy is the first line from what song?",
    option1: "Fandango",
    option2: "The Joker",
    option3: "Take The Money and Run",
    option4: "Fly Like an Eagle",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "who made lyrics innalillahi aaliyah, innalillahi mata kiri?",
    option1: "P.diddy",
    option2: "Taylor swift",
    option3: "Ishowspeed",
    option4: "Guntur",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Name the cringiest fanbase music in the world?",
    option1: "swifties",
    option2: "of course swifties",
    option3: "no offense, swifties",
    option4: "ABSOLUTELY SWIFTIES!!",
    ans: 1,
  },
];